Harry F. Brown Papers
© 2003 University of Connecticut
- Series V: 35mm Mounted Slides, consisting primarily of scenes along the electrified single-track Danbury Branch, and views of catenary modifications and other construction at New Rochelle Junction in connection with the Interstate 95 highway overpass construction, n.d., 1959, 1964
  - Subseries A: Black & White, n.d.
    - The wreckage of a New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad locomotive turned on its side on one side of a railroad track and another wrecked car on the opposite side, July 1955 (Box 9:402)
    - A view down the center of four railroad tracks and through multiple anchor bridges with industrial buildings off to the left and a neighborhood to the right, July 1955 (Box 9:403)
    - Another view down the center of four railroad tracks and through several anchor bridges with industrial buildings on the left, July 1955 (Box 9:404)
    - Another view down the center of four railroad tracks through several anchor bridges in an industrial area, July 1955 (Box 9:405)
    - Another view down the center of four railroad tracks through several anchor bridges in an industrial area, July 1955 (Box 9:406)
    - Another view further down the center of four railroad tracks and through several anchor bridges, July 1955 (Box 9:407)
    - The side of a train under an anchor bridge, July 1955 (Box 9:408)
    - A train with five visible cars on the second track from the right out of four. Three men stand on the railroad tracks in front of it, July 1955 (Box 9:409)
    - A five car train stands on the second track to the right out of four tracks with three men standing on the railroad tracks in front of it, July 1955 (Box 9:410)
    - An anchor bridge over four railroad tracks near a five car train further down the tracks. Three men stand near the train, July 1955 (Box 9:411)
    - The top of an anchor bridge over four curving tracks with a train and men on the tracks further down, July 1955 (Box 9:412)
    - A view down the center of four railroad tracks and through several anchor bridges, July 1955 (Box 9:413)
    - Four railroad tracks with multiple anchor bridges in an industrial area, July 1955 (Box 9:414)
    - Four railroad tracks with anchor bridges with a body of water on the left and an industrial area on the right, July 1955 (Box 9:415)
    - Four railroad tracks looking through multiple anchor bridges near a body of water on the left, July 1955 (Box 9:416)
    - Four railroad tracks and a platform with a body of water to the left and industrial buildings to the right, July 1955 (Box 9:417)
    - Four railroad tracks with multiple anchor bridges. Four men walk along the right side of the tracks. On a lower level to both sides is an industrial area, July 1955 (Box 9:418)
    - Four railroad tracks curving through multiple anchor bridges with industrial buildings in the background to the right, July 1955 (Box 9:419)
    - An electric locomotive with several cars behind it approaching under several anchor bridges, July 1955 (Box 9:420)
    - An anchor bridge with A-frame posts and tiers of wires above on the crossing. An industrial area surrounds the tracks, July 1955 (Box 9:421)
    - Four railroad tracks under several anchor bridges in an industrial area, July 1955 (Box 9:422)
    - A man standing on the back of a long train's caboose speaks to men who stand on the left side of the railroad tracks. The caboose is just leaving a bridge area and the train spans multiple anchor bridges, July 1955 (Box 9:423)
    - Four railroad tracks with anchor bridges stretching into the distance. A body of water is off to the right of the tracks,July 1955 (Box 9:424)
    - Four railroad tracks in an industrial area with a body of water to the right. A man stands on the tracks in the bottom right corner of the image,July 1955 (Box 9:425)
    - Four railroad tracks in an industrial area with a body of water in the distance. A train with five visible cars approaches on the second track from the right, July 1955 (Box 9:426)
    - Four railroad tracks in an industrail area with a body of water in the distance. In the left side of the image a train rounds a curve, July 1955 (Box 9:427)
    - Four railroad tracks under an anchor bridge with A-frame posts and multiple wire equipment on the crossing post. A sign by the base of the left post reads either "4284" or "4234", July 1955 (Box 9:428)
    - Four railroad tracks under multiple anchor bridges that carry multiple wire equipment on the crossing posts. A five car train moves away down the second track from the left, July 1955 (Box 9:429)
    - Four railroad tracks under multiple anchor bridges that hold equipment. Multiple wires connect to the crossing post, July 1955 (Box 9:430)
    - Four railroad tracks under multiple anchor bridges, which have catenary wires along their crossing posts and wires stretching diagonally from the side posts to the ground beside them,July 1955 (Box 9:431)
    - A close-up of the crossing post and left post of an anchor bridge with its catenary wires over four railroad tracks,July 1955 (Box 9:432)
    - At least seven, possibly eight, railroad tracks with wide and elaborate anchor bridges stretching across them. Two men stand near the right post of the closest anchor bridge to the viewer and freight train cars stand on the tracks to the left,July 1955 (Box 9:433)
    - Anchor bridges with very tall extension posts above each side post that raise the wires far above the tracks. On the left of the four tracks is a cage-like grouping of electrical equipment. The side of a railroad bridge is in the bottom right corner of the image,July 1955 (Box 9:434)
    - A complex group of wires attached to multiple anchor bridges, including the catenary wires above the four railroad tracks, wires following along the sides of the tracks, and wires stretching diagonally from the side posts of the anchor bridges to the ground,July 1955 (Box 9:435)
    - Another image of a complex grouping of wires attached to multiple anchor bridges, including catenary wires above the railroad tracks, wires following along the sides of the tracks, and wires stretching diagonally from the side posts of the anchor bridges to the ground beside them,July 1955 (Box 9:436)
    - An anchor bridge holding catenary and other wires to the right of a railroad bridge's side, July 1955 (Box 9:437)
    - Catenary wires stretching over four railroad tracks and multiple anchor bridges in an industrial area, July 1955 (Box 9:438)
    - Catenary and other wires connected to anchor bridges with side posts extending high above the crossing post that carry wires far above the tracks, July 1955 (Box 9:439)
    - Catenary over anchor bridges that carry other types of wires on extended posts both on the left side post and on the right side of the crossing post,July 1955 (Box 9:440)
    - Another view of anchor bridges that have extra equipment to hold other wires in addition to catenary wires,July 1955 (Box 9:441)
    - Another view of anchor bridges that have extra equipment to hold other wires in addition to catenary in an industrial area,July 1955 (Box 9:442)
    - Another view of anchor bridges that have extra equipment to hold other wires in addition to catenary in an industrial area,July 1955 (Box 9:443)
    - A view of catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad tracks on the anchor bridges that have extra equipment above,July 1955 (Box 9:444)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on two pieces of extra equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:445)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on two pieces of extra equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:446)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on two pieces of extra equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:447)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on two pieces of extra equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:448)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on two pieces of extra equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:449)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on two pieces of extra equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:450)
    - An anchor bridge with A-frame side posts and two pieces of extra equipment centered on the crossing post for catenary and other wires,July 1955 (Box 9:451)
    - A bar attached to the catenary wires and spanning the width of all four railroad tracks but having no support from the ground, July 1955 (Box 9:452)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad tracks on two pieces of equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:453)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad tracks on two pieces of equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:454)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad tracks on two pieces of equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:455)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad tracks on two pieces of equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:456)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad tracks on two pieces of equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:457)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad tracks on two pieces of equipment centered on the crossing post of each anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:458)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on anchor bridges. One piece of extra equipment for holding wires extends up from the right post of the anchor bridge and another rests off center to the left on the crossing post,July 1955 (Box 9:459)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on anchor bridges. One piece of extra equipment for holding wires extends up from the right post of the anchor bridge and another rests off center to the left on the crossing post,July 1955 (Box 9:460)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on anchor bridges. One piece of extra equipment for holding wires extends up from the right post of the anchor bridge and another rests off center to the left on the crossing post,July 1955 (Box 9:461)
    - Catenary and other wires following a curve in the railroad track on anchor bridges. One piece of extra equipment for holding wires extends up from the right post of the anchor bridge and another rests off center to the left on the crossing post. In addition, a tall pole stands on the crossing post, raising many wires far above the anchor bridges,July 1955 (Box 9:462)
    - An anchor bridge with two exceptinally tall poles extending up from the right post and from near the left post on the crossing post, and with a third, smaller, piece of equipment towards the center of the crossing post. All of this extra equipment carries catenary and other wires high above the anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:463)
    - An anchor bridge with two exceptinally tall poles extending up from the right post and from near the left post on the crossing post, and with a third, smaller, piece of equipment towards the center of the crossing post. All of this extra equipment carries catenary and other wires high above the anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:464)
    - A close-up view of catenary wires stretching out from the underside of an anchor bridge's crossing post,July 1955 (Box 9:465)
    - A view of catenary and other wires connected to an anchor bridge and to two extremely tall poles on it, one extending from the right post and the other from just to the right of the left post. Also holding wires is a smaller piece of equipment near the center of the crossing post,July 1955 (Box 9:466)
    - Catenary and other wires connected to an anchor bridge and to two tall poles extending up from the left and right posts of the anchor bridge,July 1955 (Box 9:467)
    - A view of an anchor bridge with catenary and other wires connecting to it,to a small piece of equipment standing near the center of the crossing post, and to two tall poles extending high into the air up from the left post and from near the right post of the crossing post,July 1955 (Box 9:468)
    - A tall triangular tower stands over the railroad tracks between many anchor bridges. Wires stretch from the top of the tower, far above the anchor bridges, and out of the image. Catenary and other wires connect to the anchor bridges and to poles extending up from their crossing posts,July 1955 (Box 9:469)
  - Subseries B: Color, n.d., 1959, 1964
    - A railway yard with an oncoming train in the top left corner and a departing train in the top right corner. Buildings are in the center positioned between two large groups of railroad tracks,May 1959 (Box 9:470)
    - A railway yard with two trains departing on the top right portion of the image. A string of railroad traffic lights and multiple electrical poles are also visible in the right portion of the slide. In the top left a group of blue railroad buildings are positioned between two groups of tracks,May 1959 (Box 9:471)
    - An outdoors, close-up image of a wire connected to electrical equipment on a pole,April 1964 (Box 9:472)
    - An outdoors, close-up image of a wire connected to electrical equipment on a pole,April 1964 (Box 9:473)
    - A single railroad track next to a brick building. A metal pole extends from the roof of the building across two metal supports, like an anchor bridge. Two wires run down the center of the crossing pole and connect to electrical equipment,April 1964 (Box 9:474)
    - A view across multiple railroad tracks near the entrance of a railroad station. Above the tracks are a complex web of electrical wires. Two cars of a passenger train are on the left side of the photo. On the right side, the back of a caboose is visible,April 1964 (Box 9:475)
    - A view from a single railroad track entering a group of tracks. Above the tracks is a complex web of electrical wires. Also in view on the right is a stop sign for the single track,April 1964 (Box 9:476)
    - A train entering under an anchor bridge in a wooded area. Attached to the anchor bridge from the side posts are two tall electrical poles which carry many wires. Equipment also extends down under the crossing post. Five pipes run along the left side of the railroad tracks, n.d. (Box 9:477)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad looking west in Stamford, Connecticut at four o'clock in the afternoon. The image was taken at the Stamford railroad station, including both platforms, railroad traffic lights, anchor bridges, triangular catenary wires and a passenger train. At least four passengers are visible on the right platform,January 10, 1959 (Box 9:478)